You know, I'm thinking about letting Emma have her first cookie.
我想着该给艾玛吃第一块饼干了
Her first cookie?
第一块
She has cookies all the time.
她常吃饼干
I've never given her a cookie.
我没喂过她饼干
- Have you? - No.
-你给她了  -没有
No. And for the record,
另外
I've also never given her frosting from a can.
我也没从罐子里拿白糖给她
Hey, Rach, the adoption agency needs letters of recommendation...
瑞秋  领养中心要我们交一份推荐信
...and we wondered if you would write one for us?
你愿意帮我们写一封吗
Of course. I would be honored.
当然愿意  这是我的荣幸
Thank you.
谢谢
I think there's been an oversight.
你们是不是疏忽了一个人
We would have asked you.
乔伊  我们本想找你
We thought you wouldn't be interested.
但又觉得你可能没兴趣
It's just that we don't think of you
我们觉得你可能
as really being so much with the words.
不擅长跟文字打交道
Clearly, we were wrong.
很明显我们错了
I got a lot of nice stuff
对于你们二位
to say about you guys, okay?
我有很多好话可写
I know how much you want to have a baby...
而且我也非常清楚你们多想要个小孩
...and I would love to help you get one.
我很想帮你们
You know what? Joey. Then we want you to do it.
好吧  乔伊  你来写
Thank you. All right. Let me see how I'm gonna start.
谢谢  我想想怎么开头
"Dear Baby Adoption Decider People...."
亲爱的婴孩领养权决定人
So excited about your letter.
迫不及待想看你写的推荐信
- Hey. - Hey, Phoebe.
-嘿  -嘿  菲比
- Wow, don't you look nice. - Yes, I do.
-你可真好看  -没错  是很美
Today's Mike and my one-year anniversary.
今天迈克和我庆祝一周年
What's it the anniversary of?
什么事情的周年
Your first date, your first kiss, first time you had sex?
第一次约会  第一次亲吻  第一次上床
Yeah.
对
So you must be going somewhere fancy to celebrate.
你们会去好地方隆重庆祝
A Knicks game.
看尼克斯队篮球比赛
Aren't you a little overdressed?
你不觉得自己穿得过于隆重了吗
I've never had a one-year anniversary before...
我从未和哪个男人有过一周年
...so no matter where we go, I'm wearing something fancy...
所以不管去哪里庆祝  我一定要盛装打扮
...I'm gonna put on my finest jewelry...
戴最好的珠宝
...and we're gonna have sex in a public restroom.
还要在公共洗手间嘿咻
You guys do that?
你们做过
Chandler won't even have sex in our bathroom.
钱德勒连在我家洗手间嘿咻也不肯
That's where people make number two.
洗手间是尿尿的地方
《老友记》第十季第五集 瑞秋的妹妹看孩子
《老友记》  第十季  第5集 瑞秋的妹妹看孩子
So, you know, I have a little time
我有点时间
if you want to....
你想不想
I'd love to, but I really have to grade these papers.
好想  但是我要判卷子
Fine. It's fine.
好  那好吧
I'll just shower by myself.
那我就自己去洗澡
B...
B...
You gave a B to a Pottery Barn catalog.
你给陶器仓库的目录上也打了个B
Well, it had some good ideas.
他们表现尚可
Take off your shirt.
脱衣服吧
- Damn it. - Rachel, open up! It's your sister!
-该死  -开门  瑞秋  你妹妹来了
I have to talk to you.
我要跟你谈谈
Hi, Amy.
嗨  艾米.
- You're not Rachel. - Still sharp as a tack.
-你不是瑞秋  -牙尖嘴利
Charlie, this is Rachel's sister Amy.
查莉  这是瑞秋的妹妹艾米
Amy, this is Charlie.
艾米  这是查莉
- Hi. Nice to meet you. - Hi, hi.
-很高兴认识你  -嗨
And you are?
你是
Ross? I grew up on your block?
罗斯  以前跟你们住一个街区
We had Thanksgiving together last year?
去年我们一起吃感恩节大餐
I had a baby with your sister?
我和你姐生了个孩子
No. I....
不  我…
falafel:以色列及部分阿拉伯国家的沙拉三明治
昨天我从你那儿买了个沙拉三明治？
Yes. Yes, you did.
没错
Hi, Rachel. Here's your sister Amy.
瑞秋  你妹妹艾米来了
She thinks I need pec implants.
她说我应该胸肌整形
Amy? Hi.
艾米  嗨
- You remember Joey. - Yeah. Hey, sure.
-记得乔伊吗  -当然
- The Days of our Lives guy. - That's right, yeah.
-《我们的日子》里的演员  -对
You are not good.
你演得真烂
Always nice to meet a fan.
见到粉丝总是让人高兴
So, now, what are you doing here?
你来干嘛
Well, I have huge news.
我有大新闻
Sorry, hold on. Let me check on the baby.
抱歉  等一下  我先看看孩子
This is important. Can't Ella wait?
我有很重要的事  艾拉不能等等
Her name is Emma.
她名叫"艾玛"
Why did you change it?
干嘛改名呀
Ella was so much prettier.
艾拉好听多了
What do I know?
我哪晓得
I just sell Middle Eastern food from a cart.
我只是推着小车卖中东食品的罢了
Hey, your English is getting better.
你英文有长进
- Oh, my God. - I know.
-天  -我知道
She may be the hottest girl I've ever hated.
她可能是我恨过的最辣的女孩
What you working on?
你干嘛呢
Monica and Chandler's recommendation.
莫妮卡和钱德勒的推荐信
I want it to sound smart,
我想让文字透着机灵劲
but I don't know any big words or anything.
但深奥的词我又不会
Why don't you use your thesaurus?
那你试试"辞典"
What did I just say?
我刚说了深奥的不会
Watch.
看着
Here, highlight the word you want to change,
选中想改的词
go under "tools" ...
在"工具"下面...
...and the thesaurus generates-- Gives.
找到"辞典"  它会"生成"... "给出"
Gives a whole list of choices.
"给出"供选词语表
You can pick the word that sounds smartest.
选一个听起来最有学问的词  就行了
My God, that's great. I'm smart.
太好了  我变聪明了
No, no, I'm:
不  我变得
"Brainy, bright, clever." I love this thing!
多智  伶俐  机敏  我爱这软件
Look out, ladies!
各位女士注意
Joey Tribbiani's got the whole package!
乔伊·崔比安尼重装上阵了
God...
天
...so beautiful.
太美了
I know, isn't she?
是啊  她好可爱
No, I was talking about your bedding.
不  我是说你的毯子
All right, what's your news, Amy?
艾米  你有啥新闻啊
Well...
呃…
...I'm getting married.
我要结婚了
Wow! Oh, my God!
我的天
- To who? - This guy.
-和谁结婚  -一个男人
He has a killer apartment.
他的房子太牛了
- And...? - And it's on Fifth.
-还有呢  -在第五大道
And the elevator opens up right into the living room.
电梯开门就到起居室
- No, what's he like? - Oh, he's okay.
-他人如何  -他还行
Do you remember my old boyfriend Mark?
还记得我以前的男朋友马克吗
- Yeah. - It's his dad.
-记得  -就是他爸
- Wow, so he's gotta be-- - Old? Yeah.
-那他可…  -太老了  对
But he travels a lot,
但他常常旅行
so he's hardly ever there.
不怎么呆在家
Sweetie, I gotta tell you,
亲爱的  不得不跟你说
it sounds a little bit like...
我怎么感觉你好象
...you like the apartment more than you like--
喜欢这房子胜过喜欢...
Myron.
米伦
Yeah, I told you he was old.
说过他年纪大嘛
Sit down.
坐下
Honey, you know...
亲爱的  你知道的
...l once also almost married somebody that I didn't love.
我也曾差一点嫁个我不爱的人
- Do you remember Barry? - Remember him?
-记得巴瑞吗  -记得他
God, we used to make out all the time after you went to sleep.
你睡了以后我们常亲热
Sometimes just nodding is okay.
有时点头回答就够了
But anyway, listen.
不管怎么样  听着
Not marrying Barry was the best decision that I ever, ever made.
没嫁给巴瑞  是我一生最英明的决定
Honey, Amy, you deserve true love.
亲爱的  你应该得到真爱
Your soul mate is out there somewhere.
你的另一半就在某处
Someone that is your age, that is smart, that is fun...
一个同龄人  聪明而有趣
...and that you care about.
你也爱他在乎他
You're right.
没错
- You're right. I'm gonna do it. - Okay.
-没错  就这么干  -好
I'm gonna marry Myron
我要嫁给米伦
and keep looking for Mr. Right.
再接着找我的另一半
Okay, let's keep talking.
接着说吧
Excuse me. Anniversary.
借过  我们过周年
Sir, could you move your nachos?
先生  请把玉米片挪挪
They're in my seat.
这是我的位子
It's my anniversary.
我们过周年
Here we are.
到了
I can't believe it's been a whole year.
真不敢相信都一年了
I know.
是啊
This has been the best year....
这是最好的一年
This has been the best year of my life!
我一辈子最快乐的一年
Me too!
同感
I never thought I could love someone this much!
从不知道会如此爱一个人
You're so generous and kind,
你慷慨  善良
and you're amazing in bed!
而且在床上总是让我欲仙欲死
It's our anniversary.
我们在庆祝周年
Knicks fans, please turn your attention
尼克斯的球迷们
to the big screen on the scoreboard.
请看记分板大屏幕这边
Someone has a special question to ask.
有人要问一个很特别的问题
How lame. It's so tacky and impersonal.
老套  俗气  丢人现眼
Really?
是吗
It's the worst way to propose.
求婚最烂的招数
Excuse me.
失陪一下
I finished my recommendation. Here.
请看我写的推荐信
And I think you'll be very, very happy.
你们看了一定会很高兴
It's the longest I ever spent on a computer
从来没这么久盯着电脑
without looking at porn.
居然没去看色情站的
I don't understand.
看不懂
Some of the words a little too sophisticated for you?
有些词汇对于你来说太深奥了
It doesn't make any sense.
都讲不通啊
Well, of course it does.
怎么可能
It's smart. I used a thesaurus.
我写得很有学问的  我用的"辞典"
On every word?
每个词都用
Yep.
没错
All right, what was this sentence originally?
这句话原本是啥意思
"They are warm, nice people with big hearts."
他们是慷慨热心的好人
And that became,
结果变成
"They are humid, prepossessing Homo sapiens...
他们是潮湿的  给人好感的智人
...with full-sized aortic pumps."
具有超额尺寸的心脏大动脉
Yeah. Yeah. And hey, I really mean it, dude.
是的  我真心这么想
All right, Joey, I don't think we can use this.
乔伊  恐怕我们不能用这封信
- Why not? - Well, because you signed it:
-为什么  -因为你的签名是
Baby Kangaroo Tribbiani:有一个卡通袋鼠形象叫乔伊
袋鼠宝宝  小崔
Why don't you stop worrying about sounding smart
算了  你还是不要假装有学问
and just be yourself.
就用你的本色来写怎么样
You don't need a thesaurus. Just write from here.
你不必用"辞典"   要用这里写
Your full-sized aortic pump.
让它发自你超额尺寸的心脏大动脉
- Amy. Hi. - I took your advice.
-艾米  嗨  -我听了你的话
- I left Myron. - Good for you!
-我跟米伦分手了  -太好了
Erin Brockovich:电影《永不妥协》主角
是啊  我简直是艾琳·布洛科维奇
Yes, you are.
对
- I'm so proud of you. - Thank you.
-以你为荣  -谢谢
So can I stay with you?
我能住你这里吗
But Erin Brockovich had her own house.
艾琳·布洛科维奇不是住她自己家吗
Look who's back.
看谁又来啦
Why do you have bags?
你怎么带行李
Rach,why does she have bags?
瑞秋  她为什么带行李
I'm staying with you guys.
我要和你们住一块了
- What? - We're gonna be roomies!
-什么  -我们成室友了
Come on.
来
- You slept out here? - Yeah.
-你睡在外面  -是啊
Amy kept kicking me in her sleep,
她梦中总踢我
yelling, "Myron, get off!"
还嚷嚷  米伦  滚出去
But we're getting rid of her, right?
我们会把她赶走对吧
Rachel,please tell me we're getting rid of her?
瑞秋  答应我  赶走她
- Joey, I can't do that. - Oh, come on.
-我下不了手  乔伊  -噢  不会吧
Last night I was finishing off a pizza,
昨晚我正在干光一个披萨
and she said
她就说
"A moment on the lips, forever on the hips."
嘴巴爽一秒  屁股胖一生
I don't need that kind of talk in my house!
在我家不需要这种屁话
Joey, look, I know that she's difficult...
乔伊  我知道她难相处
...but I think it's really good that she's here.
但她来这里也不错
Because we'll appreciate it more when she's gone?
这样她滚蛋后我们才能更欢喜
No, it's just-- Look, when I first moved to this city,
不  只是  我刚来这城市的时候
I was a lot like her.
还不是一样
I was spoiled, self-centered.
被惯坏  自我中心
And you guys really took care of me.
你们几个却照顾我
Yeah. Monica made us.
莫妮卡强迫我们来着
Well, whatever. I really appreciate it...
不管怎样我都很感激
...because I don't think I would be the person I am today...
如果没有你们
...if it wasn't for you guys.
也就没有现在的我
So I want to help Amy
我想帮帮艾米
the way you guys helped me.
就像你们帮我那样
And I know it's gonna take patience,
我知道这需要极大的耐性
but that's okay.
我可以
- Good morning. - Yeah.
-早  -早
That's what I'm wearing today.
艾米  那是我今天要穿的衣服
That's why I hung it on the door.
所以我才挂在门上
Oh, sweetie, you can't pull this off.
宝贝  你总不能给我扒下来
You know what?
你知道吗
I was thinking that maybe now would be a good time...
现在我们也许应当坐下来
...for us to sit down and, you know, talk about your future.
好好谈谈你的将来
Oh, I can't, honey.
我没空
I'm gonna go get my eyebrows shaped.
我要去修眉
I am not happy.
这样的眉毛像哭丧着脸
Sure you want to eat that?
你确定要吃吗
I'm curvy and I like it!
我不就是丰满点吗  我喜欢
- Hi. - Hi.
-嗨  -嗨
I just had the worst anniversary ever.
最烂的周年庆
I doubt that.
才不是呢
Tell her about us last year.
给她讲讲我们去年怎么过的周年
Well, I bought Chandler a $500 watch,
我给钱德勒买了一只500块的表
and he wrote me a rap song.
而他  给我写了首饶舌歌
- Seriously? - Word.
-真的  -用的办公软件
Mine was worse than that.
我的比你还逊
Well, what happened?
怎么啦
We were at the game.
球赛时
This guy proposed to his girlfriend on the big screen thing.
有人在大屏幕上求婚
That is so tacky.
老套
Well, that's what I said.
我也是那么说
But it turns out Mike was planning on
结果呢  原来迈克昨晚上就想用
proposing to me the same way last night.
这种方式向我求婚
Oh, my God. Mike was gonna propose?
天  迈克要求婚
That's huge.
大件事
Do you want to marry him?
你想嫁他吗
Yeah, I really do. Yes.
当然想啦
But after I dumped on the way he was gonna do it...
结果我那句话把他堵回去了
...l don't think he'll ever ask again.
我想他一辈子都不会求婚了
I said no in Barbados, and now this?
在巴贝多斯我拒绝过他一次了  现在又一次
She's right. If I were a guy and....
没错  如果我是男人
Did I just say, "lf I were a guy"?
我刚才是不是说  如果我是男人
You don't need him to propose to you.
别等他求婚了
Maybe you could propose to him.
主动出击吧
Oh, I don't know.
哦  不知道
I don't know. Isn't that a little desperate?
我又不是想嫁想疯了
I proposed to Chandler.
我向钱德勒求的婚
All right, moving on.
好吧  继续讲
I don't think it was desperate.
我不觉得你想嫁想疯了
It was amazing.
我觉得你很棒
Thank you.
谢谢
Well, do you think I should propose?
你们都认为我该求婚
I think it could be kind of great.
那一定很棒
Absolutely.
当然
You'll love the feeling.
世上再没有比求婚
There's nothing like it.
更美妙的感觉了
Okay. Okay. So how should I do it?
好  那么以何种方式呢
How about at a game on the big screen?
就在球赛的大屏幕上啊
How about at a Foot Locker?
那去体育用品专卖店吧
What? What, he obviously thinks
他既然选择过大屏幕求婚
that's a nice way to be proposed to.
可见他能接受这种方式
Plus, he'd never suspect it.
而且他也不会起疑心
Yeah, that does make sense.
有理
Okay, now, would you two like that?
你们会喜欢吗
Sounds good to me.
我喜欢
But what would a guy think?
不过男性会怎么想
- Nana's on the phone. - Wow.
-奶奶电话  -哇
That's interesting,
有趣
since she died seven years ago.
她七年前就死了
She did?
是吗
Who got her condo in Boca?
那她在博卡的房子归谁了
Hello?
喂
It's our nanny.
是我们的保姆
Oh, God, I hope you feel better. Okay. Bye.
是吗  希望你早点康复  再见
That's Molly. She's sick.
是莫利  她病了
Can you watch Emma today?
今天你看艾玛可以吗
I can't. I have back-to-back classes.
不行  我要连堂上课
Did Molly say what she had?
莫利说她生什么病
Because my throat's been hurting.
我的喉咙也不舒服
Menstrual cramps.
痛经
I don't think that's what this is.
我可能不是这毛病
Can any of you watch Emma?
你们帮忙看着艾玛成吗
No, I'm sorry, sweetie.
抱歉  亲爱的
No, I've got work, and then I'm proposing.
我要上班  还要求婚
Great. Shoot. What am I gonna do?
糟糕  那怎么办
Well, I could do it.
我可以帮忙
Well, actually....
好  实际上...
Can I talk to you for a second?
能跟你说句话吗
I do not want her babysitting our child.
我不想让她看我们的孩子
Why not?
为啥
For one thing, she keeps calling her Ella.
首先  她老是把我们的孩子喊成"艾拉"
Ella's a nice name.
这名字也不错嘛
Fine, we'll call the next one Ella.
好  下一胎叫"艾拉"
- The next one? - Okay.
-下一胎  -好
I don't want her watching our baby.
我不赞成她帮我们看孩子
Ross, I am trying to help her become a better person.
我只是想改造她
This is a huge breakthrough for her.
这是个好机会
She just offered to do something
她刚刚主动要求
for another human being.
帮助别的人类了
You know, I don't know.
我不确定
Ross, I'm telling you...
罗斯  我是说
...she's giving up getting her eyebrows shaped to do this, all right?
她宁愿牺牲修眉的时间看孩子
Do you understand
你知道这件事
how important that is in our world?
对我们女人来说牺牲多重大吗
Listen, I couldn't help but overhear,
我不小心听到你们的谈话
because I was trying to.
因为我想听
Listen, let me do this.
就让我带孩子吧
I really want to help you guys out.
我真心想帮你们
And plus, Rachel's been so wonderful to me.
而且  瑞秋对我太好了
- Absolutely. - Oh, great!
-好  -太好了
So how much does it pay?
付多少工钱
Hi,Joe.
乔伊
How's the second draft of the letter coming?
二稿如何
Great. I'm finished.
很好  我已经写完了
In fact, I just dropped it off at the agency.
实际上  我已经交了
- You dropped it off? - Yeah.
-交了  -是啊
Can we read it?
我们能读读吗
Can you print out another copy?
能再打印一份给我们吗
No can do, amigo.
恐怕不行啊  朋友
No, I didn't use the computer.
没用电脑
It felt more personal to handwrite it.
手写的  显得更亲切
- You handwrote it? - Yeah, and don't worry.
-还手写  -别担心
I didn't try to sound smart at all.
我根本没有装聪明
See you later.
再见
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
我的天  我的天
That letter is gonna go in our file.
那信会放入我们的档案里
We're never gonna get a kid.
我们这辈子别想有孩子了
We're gonna be one of those old couples...
我们会孤独终老
...that collects orchids or has a lot of birds.
养花弄鸟
It's okay. You know what?
没事的
I will just call the agency
我打电话给领养中心
and tell them to throw out the letter.
请他们扔掉那封信
Okay, good.
好
Hello, this is Chandler Bing.
喂  我是钱德勒·宾
Someone just dropped off
有人手写了
a handwritten recommendation letter and....
一封推荐信
Okay.
好
Thank you. Goodbye.
谢谢  再见
We're screwed, aren't we?
我们完蛋了  是不是
You know what?
这样吧
Just tell me on the way to the bird store.
买鸟的路上说给我听
- They loved it. - What?
-他们喜欢那封信  -什么
They thought it was very smart of us
他们说我们很聪明
to have a child write the letter.
叫个小孩写推荐信
They thought Joey was a child?
他们以为乔伊是小孩
She guessed 8, 9, based on his drawings.
她看了他的画  以为他只八九岁
- Hi. - Hey, what'd you guys do today?
-嗨  -嗨  你们今天干嘛了
Ella wanted to go out,
艾拉想上街
so we went shopping and got some sushi.
所以我们去购物  还吃了寿司
- That sounds like fun. - Yeah, not really.
-有趣  -也不是啦
Babies are dull.
婴儿都好无趣
- Hey. Hi, how's my girl? - I'm fine.
-我家小妹妹怎样了  -我很好
And I got you a present
我准备送你礼物
for letting me stay with you.
来谢谢你留我住
- Ready? - Yeah.
-准备好了  -嗯
You pierced her ears?
你给她穿了耳洞
Doesn't it make her nose look smaller?
她的鼻子看来小点了吗
How could you do this without telling me?
竟然不征求我同意
If I had told you,
我若先告诉你
then it wouldn't have been a surprise, now would it?
就不是惊喜了
I think she looks cute.
我觉得她看来很可爱
But I am wrong.
但我错了
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Here comes Ross.
我的天啊  罗斯来了
He's gonna flip out.
罗斯会发飚的
Why, did something happen
为什么  他卖三明治的推车
to his falafel cart?
让城管收了吗
- Hey, guys. - Ross!
-嗨  各位  -罗斯
Hi, Emma.
嗨  艾玛
Why is she wearing her hat so low?
她的帽子干嘛压这么低
She can barely see.
她都看不见了
I don't really want her to see.
人家不想她看见嘛
Why not?
为啥
Because there are so many terrible sights in this world.
世界太可怕
Like war. Or that thing in Joey's refrigerator. Remember?
有战争  还有乔伊冰箱里那玩意儿
It was in a milk carton, but it looked like meat?
一只牛奶盒  但看来像块肉
Come here.
快来
There she is. Hi.
看她多乖
- What? - Nothing.
-怎么啦  -没啥
Hi.
嗨
What--?
什么
Please tell me those are clip-ons!
那是夹上去的吧
Oh, they're real.
是扎的耳洞
Did she do this to her?
是她干的
I told you
我早说过
we shouldn't have left Emma with her!
不能把艾玛交到她手上
I know, I know. And you were right, Ross.
我知道了  你说得对
Okay? You are so irresponsible!
你太不负责
I am never letting you babysit again!
绝不再让你看孩子
You know what? This kid needs me, okay?
你们知道吗  她需要我
She needs to have a cool, fun aunt.
她需要一个又酷又有趣的阿姨
I'm a cool, fun aunt.
我就是
Okay.
好吧
Hey! Monica can be cool and fun
莫妮本来就是又酷又有趣
at organized indoor projects.
而且有条有理
All I wanted to do was help you
我只不过想帮你
try to figure out what to do with your life.
想清楚你将来想干什么
This is how you repay me?
结果呢  你还是小孩子
I don't need you to help me.
谁稀罕你帮忙
Because I already know what I'm gonna do with my life.
我自己早想好我的人生要干什么了
- Oh, yeah? Since when? - Since today.
-是吗  几时想好的  -今天
I am going to be a baby stylist.
我要当婴儿时尚专家
- What? - That's not a thing!
-啊  -有这职业吗
Well, it should be.
该有
I'm gonna help babies learn how to accessorize...
我要教婴儿如何配饰
...what colors to wear,
选衣裳的颜色
what clothes are slimming.
什么衣服较瘦身
Babies don't care if they're slim!
婴儿才不管苗条不苗条
Enter Amy.
如何像艾米一样美
Amy, l-- I just-- I just wanna--
艾米  我要…
What? What are you gonna do?
你想怎样
No more falafel for you!
罚你永世没有三明治吃
Great game, huh?
比赛很精彩
Why do you keep looking at the screen?
你怎么老瞄大屏幕
I'm not. I'm praying.
没  我在祷告
Please let the Knicks win.
请让尼克斯队赢吧
Thank you, Thor.
谢谢你  雷神
Where are you going?
你上哪儿
I'm going to the bathroom.
嘘嘘去
Well, I think you should wait.
等一会
Why?
为啥
Well, if you don't hold it in,
如果不憋一会
you don't get all the nutrients.
你就无法摄取所有养分
Knicks fans, please turn your attention
尼克斯球迷
to the big screen on the scoreboard.
请注意记分牌大屏幕
Someone has a special question to ask.
有人要问特别的问题
Mike Hannigan, will you marry me?
迈克·汉尼根  我们结婚吧
Get a load of this. She's proposing to him!
看啊  女人向男人求婚
Guess we know who wears the pants in that family.
我们知道谁是爷们了
Well, that's not very enlightened.
不要误导观众
Boo us? Boo you!
不许嘘我们
Hello? Yeah, this is Joey Tribbiani.
喂  我就是乔伊·崔比安尼
Oh, hi.
哦  嗨
Well, I'm glad you liked my letter.
真高兴你喜欢我的信
No, my mommy and daddy aren't home right now.
不  我爸妈不在家
Okay, bye-bye.
再见
She was nice.
这人真好
Joey, get Amy's bags. She is moving out.
乔伊  把艾米的箱子拿出来  她要搬走了
You're kicking me out?
你要把我赶出去
You put holes in my baby's ears.
你给我的女儿穿耳洞
At least now people will know she's a girl!
不然大家怎么知道她是女孩
I can't believe I ever even tried to help you.
不敢相信  我竟然想过要帮你
- You are so beyond help! - You know what?
-你不可救药  -你知道吗
Ever since I got here, you have been nothing but negative.
这次见面你在否定我的一切
- Excuse me? - You didn't want me...
-你说什么  -你不准我…
...to marry the old guy with the great apartment.
嫁有豪宅的老头
Then I tried to help your daughter de-emphasize her flaws...
我想帮你把你女儿的鼻子变小点
...and suddenly I'm the bad guy?
结果吃力不讨好
Joey, where are those bags?
乔伊  行李怎么还没搬出来
She has a lot of crap!
她的破玩意太多了
You know? When I moved in here,
我刚搬来时
I thought, "This will be so great.
还憧憬姐妹团聚
Just us sisters back together again like when we were kids."
像童年那样
Except without that stupid Jill.
而且没有该死的吉尔捣乱
Who has gotten fat, by the way.
她变肥了
Seriously?
真的
Mom said she gained, like, 15 pounds.
妈说吉尔肥了15磅
- Hips or thighs? - Ass and face.
-屁股和大腿长肉了  -屁股和脸
Oh, my God! I thought she was on Atkins.
天啊  她不是节食吗
She was. Carbs found her.
本来是  但是还是没能抵挡碳水化合物的诱惑
See? This is what I wanted.
看  这才像姐妹
Two sisters talking about real stuff.
真心交谈
Oh, I can give you that.
哦  我可以这样
- You can? - Yeah.
-你可以  -是的
I kept trying to make you a better person, but you're....
我老想改造你  实际上
You're already a pretty perfect version of what you are.
你本来就接近完美了
Thank you.
谢谢你
You gotta admit, Emma does look cute.
必须承认  艾玛真可爱
Did you just say, "Emma"?
你刚说"艾玛"
Oh, I'm sorry. Ella.
对不起  艾拉
That woman didn't know what she was talking about, Mike.
赛场里那女人真是乱讲
Obviously, you have balls.
你当然有种
Please, let's forget the whole thing.
忘了算了
I would love it.
你能忘最好
Consider it forgotten.
已经忘了
Thank you.
谢谢
But just so you know....
但是我要你知道
However and whenever you decide to propose,
不管你何时以何方式求婚
I promise I'll say yes.
我保证都答应
Whether, you know, it's at a basketball game...
不管是篮球赛
...or in skywriting...
还是用飞机在空中拉条幅
...or, you know, like some lame guy in a cheesy movie...
或是像一些滥电影里
...who hides it in the cake.
把求婚戒指藏在蛋糕里
It's in the cake, isn't it?
藏蛋糕里了  对吧
Where else would lame Mr. No Balls hide it?
没种的男人还会有什么好点子吗
What's the matter with me?
老是毁坏你的一番美意
Why do I keep ruining this?
怎么老提这个
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起  真对不起
No, it's my fault.
是我错
I keep trying to propose in these stupid ways...
我老用愚蠢的方式求婚
...and I just wanna tell you I love you,
我只是想告诉你  我爱你
and I wanna spend my life with you....
我想和你过余生
I'm gonna do this now.
我现在求婚
Oh, my God.
天啊
Phoebe, l--
菲比
Wait. Oh, wait.
等等
Okay.
好了
Ready? Okay.
可以了
Phoebe, I love you.
菲比  我爱你
There's no one else in the world
世界上没一个女人
I would ask to marry me three times.
能让我费尽心机来求三次婚
But I want to take care of you...
我想照顾你
...have babies with you...
和你生儿育女
...and grow old with you.
一起变老
Phoebe Buffay, will you marry me?
菲比·布菲  你愿意嫁我吗
Yes.
我愿意
- I love you. - I love you more.
-我爱你  -我爱你更多
Not possible.
不可能
She's gonna be Mrs. No Balls!
她是"没种夫人"了
So how's the baby-styling business going?
婴儿时尚专家的事情怎么样了
Not that great.
行情不大好
It's almost as if people don't want
好象大家都不爱听
to hear that their babies are ugly.
别人说他家的孩子丑
That's shocking.
还有这事儿
There's Ross. Hey, Ross.
那不是罗斯吗  罗斯
Hello, Ross?
你好  罗斯
He's rude.
真没教养